

✓ rpark@gmail.com

✓ (123) 456 78 99

✓ Alabama

Website

Professional Summary

Over 8 years of experience in design and development of User Interface applications, integrating with numerous databases and Client-Server applications of iOS using Objective-C, SQL, Cocoa Touch, Cocoa Bindings, and Around 5 years experience working with iOS frameworks such as Core Data, Core Animation, Core Graphics, UI Kit and Event Kit Framework.

Work Experience

Senior los Developer/Instructor

AT&T Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Atlanta, GA

- Lead and coordinated weekly meetings and live demos at client site.
- Reconstructed UI with new menu navigation using Added Auto Layout constraints to conform UI Controls to desired layout.
- Created overview screen with accompanying Delegation pattern, based on wireframes given, simplifying access to usage information.

Senior los Developer

Delta Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Los Angeles, CA

- Description: Sears mobile application provides the convenience of online shopping through mobile devices.
- User can shop millions of products from this application.
- This application provides a fun ecommerce experience where users can manage their online accounts, find help from a personal shopper, manage their shopping cart, track the status of their orders, find local ads, deals and nearest store locations for store pick up etc.

Education

Bachelor's In Science In Electrical Engineering

University Of Texas - Arlington, TX Jan / 2019 - Ongoing New York

Skills			
iOS	XCode	00P	MVC
		0	
Swift			

Achievements

Award